necklace2 =[
  {"question":"出乎","Answer":"chūhū"},
  {"question":"意料","Answer":"yìliào"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"邀請函","Answer":"yāoqǐnghán"},
  {"question":"淚眼汪汪","Answer":"lèiyǎnwāngwāng"},
  {"question":"出席宴會","Answer":"chūxí yànhuì"},
  {"question":"邀請函","Answer":"yāoqǐnghán"},
  {"question":"皺了皺眉頭","Answer":"zhòu le zhòuméitóu"},
  {"question":"一套","Answer":"yītào"},
  {"question":"大概","Answer":"dàgài"},
  {"question":"法郞","Answer":"fǎ láng"},
  {"question":"丈夫","Answer":"zhàngfu"},
  {"question":"震驚","Answer":"zhènjīng"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"哭喪着臉","Answer":"kūsàngzheliǎn"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"搭配","Answer":"dāpèi"},
  {"question":"珠寶","Answer":"zhūbǎo"},
  {"question":"靈機一動","Answer":"língjīyīdòng"},
  {"question":"件","Answer":"jiàn"},
  {"question":"珍","Answer":"zhēn"},
  {"question":"馬蹄達","Answer":"mǎtí dá"},
  {"question":"難堪","Answer":"nánkān"},
  {"question":"鑲","Answer":"xiāng"},
  {"question":"寶石","Answer":"bǎoshí"},
  {"question":"箱子","Answer":"xiāngzi"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"嗯","Answer":"en"},
  {"question":"挑","Answer":"tiāo"},
  {"question":"首飾","Answer":"shǒushì"},
  {"question":"失神","Answer":"shīshén"},
  {"question":"撫摸","Answer":"fǔmō"},
  {"question":"猶豫","Answer":"yóuyù"},
  {"question":"絲綢","Answer":"sīchóu"},
  {"question":"獻寶","Answer":"xiànbǎo"},
  {"question":"瞠目結舌","Answer":"chēngmùjiéshé"},
  {"question":"倒抽","Answer":"dǎo chōu"},
  {"question":"涼氣","Answer":"liángqì"},
  {"question":"哇","Answer":"wā"},
  {"question":"鑽石項鏈","Answer":"zuànshí xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"項鏈","Answer":"xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"嗯","Answer":"en"},
  {"question":"瑪蒂達","Answer":"mǎdì dá"},
  {"question":"鑽石項鏈","Answer":"zuànshí xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"","Answer":""},
  {"question":"顫抖","Answer":"chàndǒu"},
  {"question":"宴會","Answer":"yànhuì"},
  {"question":"來臨","Answer":"láilín"},
  {"question":"穿戴華麗","Answer":"chuāndài huálì"},
  {"question":"項鍊","Answer":"xiàngliàn"}
 ]